

Ana Laura Navas Cañas

Date of birth: 09/07/2002 Nationality: Salvadoran

CONTACT

El Salvador (Home)



lauranavasv@gmail.com



(+503) 79570450



github.com/lauranavas



ABOUT MF

I'm a web developer with experience in customer service. My passion for technology, analysis, and problem-solving has honed my ability to find efficient and effective solutions in web development. As a member of the World Organization of the Scout Movement, I value teamwork and leadership, allowing me to collaborate effectively on programming projects. I'm committed to volunteering and serving my community, bringing these values to my work. My skills in problem-solving and dedication to excellence make me an ideal candidate for any project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

13/01/2023 - CURRENT El Salvador

Language school teacher Start English and Yo Sí Aprendo Inglés

 Prepare didactic material to create engaging, appealing, dynamic, and fun private 1-on-1 classes for students.

- Provide outstanding personalized classes that cater to the individual needs of each student.

— Ensure that students receive the attention and support they require to achieve their language learning goals.

 Continuously evaluate and adapt teaching methods to maximize learning outcomes.

18/10/2022 - CURRENT El Salvador

Graphic designer Start English and Yo Sí Aprendo Inglés

- $\boldsymbol{-}$ Creation of custom graphic designs, including logos, infographics, and designs for social media.
- Development of creative concepts.
- Editing of images and photographs.
- Editing of educational and entertainment videos.
- Updating and modifying existing designs according to the company's
- Editorial design.

30/11/2020 – 01/01/2023 Calle Chiltiupan y, 17 Avenida Nte., Santa Tecla, El Salvador

Customer service representative Telus International

 Provide high-quality customer service and technical support to users of the MoneyGram International application and website.

— Handle calls in the escalations department as a supervisor. Train and provide mentorship to new hires on the guidelines of

MoneyGram International and Telus International.

13/02/2019 – 13/10/2019 Av. Olímpica, San Salvador, El Salvador

Software developer Gráfica Fénix

 Design and develop a web application using PHP, MySQL, and HTML/ CSS to efficiently manage the process of receiving, creating, and delivering services in the printing and graphic design field.

- Create an intuitive and attractive user interface using web design

tools to enhance the user experience in the application.

— Implement automation features in the web application to streamline and optimize the workflow in service management.

- Document the code and provide clear instructions to facilitate future maintenance and scalability of the application.

- Collaborate with other developers to ensure effective synergy and a successful end result.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

02/01/2023 - CURRENT

Full Stack JavaScript The Odin Project

Website www.theodinproject.com

01/01/2018 - 16/11/2020 San Salvador , El Salvador

Vocational Technical High School Diploma in Software Development Instituto Técnico Ricaldone

Address Avenida Aguilares 218, San Salvador , El Salvador | **Website** <u>www.ricaldone.edu.sv</u>

22/01/2020 - 13/04/2020

Web Development Foundations The Odin Project

Website www.theodinproject.com

01/03/2020 - 09/04/2020

M001: Foundations MongoDB Mongo University

Website www.learn.mongodb.com

21/03/2019 - 04/05/2019

CCNA Routing and Switching: Introduction to Networks Instituto Técnico Ricaldone en colaboración con Cisco Networking Academy

Website www.netacad.com

11/03/2018 - 21/03/2018

Female Leadership Embajada de Nueva Zelanda en El Salvador

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Spanish

Other language(s):

English

Listening C1	Reading C1	Spoken production C1	Spoken interaction C1	Writing C1
Portuguese				
Listening A2	Reading B1	Spoken production A2	Spoken interaction A2	Writing A2

DIGITAL SKILLS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

JavaScript | SQL | Linux | CSS | HTML | NoSQL | Git

DOCUMENTATION

Microsoft Office | Google Workspace

GRAPHIC DESIGN

Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Illustrator

UI/UX DESIGN

Adobe XD | Figma